Register of the Karl August Wittfogel papers, 1728-1992
Hoover Institution Archives
- CORRESPONDENCE, 1907-1988.
  - Columbia University (Ainslie T. Embree, John A. Krout, Andrew L. March, Stephen A. McCarthy, Peter Robert Roux)
    - 1961-1980 (Folder 27)
  - Combat, 1970 (Folder 28)
  - Commentary (Elliot E. Cohen, Nathan Glazer, Martin Greenberg), 1950-1956 (Folder 29)
  - Committee for a Free China (Lee Edwards), 1972-1975 (Folder 30)
  - Committee for the Study of Individual Freedom (Donald L. Kemmerer, Seward E. Robb, Francis G. Wilson), 1962-1963 (Folder 31)
  - Committee of One Million (Marvin Liebman), 1957-1958. Includes correspondence with Friends of Free China Association (Folder 32)
  - Compton, Boyd, 1959 (Folder 33)
  - Congress for Cultural Freedom. Japan Committee (Hoki Isihara, Yasuharu Shimamura), 1952-1963 (Box 14., Folder 1)
  - Conklin, Harold C., 1960 (Folder 2)
  - Conlon, Frank F., 1968 (Folder 3)
  - Conolly, Violet, 1955-1961 (Folder 4)
  - Conservative Book Club, 1964-1978 (Folder 5)
  - Constas, Helen. Includes correspondence with Arlington House Publishers, Collier Books, Conservative Book Club, Henry Regnery Company, Eleanora A. Cebotarev, Roy N. Schantz
    - 1954-1964 (Folder 6)
    - 1965-1971 (Folder 7)
  - Contemporary China (Ronald Hsia), 1958-1959 (Folder 8)
  - Contrat Social, 1957-1961 (Folder 9)
  - Conze, E. J. D., 1966 (Folder 10)
  - Coomaraswamy, Ananda K., 1946 (Folder 11)
  - Coplan, Edna, 1970-1983 (Folder 12)
  - Cornell, Richard, 1970 (Folder 13)
  - Coste, Brutus, 1967 (Folder 14)
  - Couch, William T., 1967 (Folder 15)
  - Council Against Communist Aggression (Arthur G. McDowell), 1952-1974 (Folder 16)
  - Council for an American Foreign Policy (Frank S. Meyer), 1964 (Folder 17)
  - Counts, George S., 1954-1962 (Folder 18)
  - Crawford, Robert B., 1960 (Folder 19)
  - Creel, Herrlee G., 1947-1949 (Folder 20)
  - Crocker, W. R., 1950 (Folder 21)
  - Crowell-Collier Publishing Company. See Collier Books
  - Current Digest of the Soviet Press, 1962-1974 (Folder 22)
  - Cuzan, Alfred G., 1980 (Folder 23)
  - D. Reidel Publishing Company, 1962-1967 (Box 15., Folder 1)
  - Dallin, Alexander, 1960-1966 (Folder 2)
  - Dallin, David, 1958 (Folder 3)
  - Das, S. R. Mohan, 1952-1957 (Folder 4)
  - Davies, John, Jr., 1948-1950 (Folder 5)
  - Dawson, Owen L., 1961 (Folder 6)
  - Deakin, F. William, 1963-1965 (Folder 7)
  - DeBary, Paul, 1964 (Folder 8)
  - DeBary, William Theodore and Fanny, 1955-1985 (Folder 9)
  - Decsy, Gyula, 1974-1980 (Folder 10)
  - Decter, Moshe, 1957-1966 (Folder 11)
  - Dedalo Libri, 1966-1967 (Folder 12)
  - Defense Intelligence School, 1968 (Folder 13)
  - De Francis, John, 1938-1948 (Folder 14)
  - Dekker, Andre G., 1971 (Folder 15)
  - Denlinger, Paul B., 1956-1967 (Folder 16)
  - Denmark. Embassy (United States), 1967 (Folder 17)
  - Desai, A. R., 1972 (Folder 18)
  - Descartes, Rene M., 1976-1978 (Folder 19)
  - De Toledano, Ralph, 1955-1958 (Folder 20)
  - Deutsch, Harold C., 1955-1965 (Folder 21)
  - Deutsche Verlags-Anstalt, 1959-1978 (Folder 22)
  - Deverall, Richard L.-G., 1951-1955 (Folder 23)
  - Devereux, George, 1947-1948 (Folder 24)
  - Diasio, Matthew, 1971 (Folder 25)
  - Dittmar, W. R., 1945-1946 (Folder 26)
  - Dodd, Bella V., 1966 (Folder 27)
  - Dodd, Thomas J., 1965 (Folder 28)
  - Domes, Jurgen, 1974 (Folder 29)
  - Donnithorne, Audrey, 1970-1986 (Folder 30)
  - Donovan, Joseph P., 1962 (Folder 31)
  - Donovan, William J., 1953-1955 (Folder 32)
  - Douglas, Paul, 1952 (Folder 33)
  - Drachkovitch, Milorad, 1959-1965 (Folder 34)
  - Drake, F. S., 1958 (Folder 35)
  - Drechsler, Hellmuth, 1952 (Folder 36)
  - Drischler, William Frederick, 1974-1984. Includes correspondence with New International Review (Folder 37)
  - Drucker, Erich, 1960-1977 (Box 16., Folder 1)
  - Drury, Dewitt and Ruth, 1968-1971 (Folder 2)
  - Dubs, Homer H., 1939-1954 (Folder 3)
  - Dull, Jack L., 1967-1979 (Folder 4)
  - Dunne, George H., 1962 (Folder 5)
  - Dunner, Joseph and Ruth, 1957-1975 (Folder 6)
  - Dyke, Walter, n.d. (Folder 7)
  - Eastman, Max, 1950-1955 (Folder 8)
  - Eberhard, Wolfram, 1935-1948 (Folder 9)
  - Edelstein, Alex, 1959 (Folder 10)
  - Edgerton, Franklin, 1946-1948 (Folder 11)
  - Ediciones Guadarrama, 1962-1975 (Folder 12)
  - Ediciones Rialp, 1963-1966 (Folder 13)
  - Edition Dokumente der Weltrevolution (Franz Ebner), 1965-1974 (Folder 14)
  - Editions de Minuit. See also Munier, Jean-Jacques; Souvarine, Boris; United States Information Agency
    - 1960-1961 (Box 17., Folder 1)
    - 1962-1963 (Folder 2)
    - 1964 (Folder 3)
    - 1965 (Folder 4)
    - 1966 (Folder 5)
    - 1967-1985 (Folder 6)
  - Editions du Seuil, 1963 (Folder 7)
  - Edizioni della Nuova Antalogia, 1969-1971 (Folder 8)
  - Edizioni Morcelliana, 1965 (Folder 9)
  - Edwards, E. D., 1950 (Folder 10)
  - Eggau, G., 1947 (Folder 11)
  - Eichler, Willi, 1961-1971 (Folder 12)
  - Eisler-Fischer, Louise, 1977 (Folder 13)
  - Elisseeff, Serge, 1940-1949 (Folder 14)
  - Ellis, Florence, 1959 (Folder 15)
  - Ellison, Herbert Jay, 1961-1975 (Folder 16)
  - Embree, Ainslie T., 1961-1973 (Folder 17)
  - Emeneau, Murray B., 1948 (Folder 18)
  - Emmerich, Herbert, 1947-1969 (Folder 19)
  - Emmet, Christopher, 1949-1967 (Folder 20)
  - Encounter (Irving Kristol), 1953-1970 (Folder 21)
  - Encyclopedia Americana, 1967 (Folder 22)
  - Enderle, Irmgard and August, 1945 (Folder 23)
  - Epstein, Fritz T., 1978 (Folder 24)
  - Epstein, William, 1970 (Folder 25)
  - Erasmus, 1962 (Folder 26)
  - Erd, Rainer, 1980-1985 (Folder 27)
  - Erich Drucker Books, 1963-1975 (Folder 28)
  - Erlich, Victor, 1950-1962 (Folder 29)
  - Ernst, Morris L., 1951 (Folder 30)
  - Esteva Fabregat, Claudio, 1957-1972 (Box 18., Folder 1)
  - Europaische Verlagsanstalt, 1950-1971 (Folder 2)
  - Evans, Austin P., 1946-1951 (Folder 3)
  - Fackenthal, Frank Diehl, 1957. See also Columbia University (Folder 4)
  - Fagg, John E., 1963 (Folder 5)
  - Fainsod, Merle, 1966 (Folder 6)
  - Fairbank, John King, 1943-1967 (Folder 7)
  - Fang, Chao-ying and Lineche, 1939-1967 (Folder 8)
  - Far Eastern Association (John A. Harrison, Hyman Kublin, George E. Taylor, C. Martin Wilbur), 1950-1955 (Folder 9)
  - Far-Eastern Prehistory Association, 1958-1961 (Folder 10)
  - Far Eastern Quarterly. See Journal of Asian Studies
  - Farb, Peter, 1964 (Folder 11)
  - Farquharson, Alexander, 1937-1949 (Folder 12)
  - Farrell, James T., 1950-1954 (Folder 13)
  - Faust, Grethe and Helmuth, 1958 (Folder 14)
  - Fei, Hsiao-tung, 1945 (Folder 15)
  - Feng, Chia-sheng, 1939-1950 (Folder 16)
  - Feng, H. D., 1937 (Folder 17)
  - Ferguson, C. Wess and Eileen, 1961-1984 (Folder 18)
  - Ferguson, Homer, 1951-1954 (Folder 19)
  - Festschrift in Honor of Prof. Karl H. Menges (C. D. Dimov-Bogoev), 1970-1971. See also Beyer, Rolf; Decsy, Gyula; Eisler-Fischer, Louise (Folder 20)
  - Fetscher, Iring, 1963 (Folder 21)
  - Field, Frederick V., 1934-1939 (Folder 22)
  - Fine, Morris, 1949 (Folder 23)
  - Fink, Lotte, 1937-1957 (Folder 24)
  - Fischel, Walter J., 1958 (Folder 25)
  - Fischer, Alfred Joachim, 1966-1967 (Folder 26)
  - Fischer, George, 1947 (Folder 27)
  - Fischer, Hugo, 1952 (Folder 28)
  - Fischer, Louis, 1960 (Folder 29)
  - Fischer, Ruth, 1948-1954 (Folder 30)
  - Fisher, Harold H., 1953 (Folder 31)
  - Fiszman, Joseph R., 1953-1955 (Folder 32)
  - Flinders University of South Australia, 1970 (Folder 33)
  - Flood, Edward T., 1962 (Folder 34)
  - Florinsky, Michael T., 1960-1963 (Folder 35)
  - Flynn, John T., 1953 (Folder 36)
  - Fockema Andreae, S. J., 1958-1963 (Box 19., Folder 1)
  - Forbes, Ir. R. J., 1951 (Folder 2)
  - Ford Foundation (Franklin A. Lindsay, Don K. Price, Carl B. Spaeth), 1952-1955. Includes correspondence with Raymond B. Allen and Jay Lovestone (Folder 3)
  - Foreign Affairs (Hamilton Fish Armstrong), 1952-1960 (Folder 4)
  - Forster, Clifford, 1954-1980 (Folder 5)
  - Fraenkel, Ernst, 1950 (Folder 6)
  - Fraenkel, Gerd, 1959-1962 (Folder 7)
  - France. Embassy (United States), 1963-1964 (Folder 8)
  - Frank, Karl, 1947-1949 (Folder 9)
  - Franke, Herbert, 1948-1986 (Folder 10)
  - Fraser, James H., 1985-1986 (Folder 11)
  - Frederick A. Praeger Inc., 1954-1965 (Folder 12)
  - Free China Fund, 1958-1961 (Folder 13)
  - Free Trade Union Committee (Jay Lovestone), 1952-1956 (Folder 14)
  - Freed, Ruth S., 1976 (Folder 15)
  - Freedom House, 1954-1973 (Folder 16)
  - Freeman, Ethel Cutler, 1968 (Folder 17)
  - Freeman, 1957-1958 (Folder 18)
  - Freudenthal, Hanna, 1936-1938 (Folder 19)
  - Fried, Morton H., 1958-1967 (Folder 20)
  - Friedheim, P., 1966-1967 (Folder 21)
  - Friedrich, Carl J., 1943-1961 (Folder 22)
  - Fries, Margaret E., n.d. (Folder 23)
  - Friess, Horace L., 1943 (Folder 24)
  - Fu, Lo-huan, 1947 (Folder 25)
  - Fuhrmann, Ernst, 1947 (Folder 26)
  - Fujieda, Akira, 1948-1967 (Folder 27)
  - Fujimaki, Shimpei, 1958 (Folder 28)
  - Fundacion Bolsa de Comercio de Buenos Aires, 1962 (Folder 29)
  - Fung, Yu-lan, 1947 (Folder 30)
  - Funken (Erna Blomeyer), 1954 (Folder 31)
  - Furse, Elizabeth, 1980-1983 (Folder 32)
  - Gale, Esson M., 1948-1950 (Folder 33)
  - Gallagher, Barrett, 1968 (Folder 34)
  - Gallas, Helga, 1968-1971 (Folder 35)
  - Gamble, Sidney D., 1940 (Folder 36)
  - Gandhi, Indira, 1976. Includes correspondence with Bertram D. Wolfe and Harry Goldberg (Folder 37)
  - Gaspardone, E., 1950 (Folder 38)
  - Gay, Peter, 1961 (Folder 39)
  - Gayda Press, 1962 (Folder 40)
  - Geiger, Bernhard, 1949 (Folder 41)
  - Geisenheyer and Crone, 1987 (Folder 42)
  - Geist, James J., 1968-1969 (Folder 43)
  - Geist und Tat (Willi Eichler), 1961-1970 (Folder 44)
  - Georg Thieme Verlag, 1970 (Folder 45)
  - George Allen and Unwin Ltd., 1954 (Folder 46)
  - Georgetown University (Karl H. Cerny, G. Paul Holman, Jr., James B. Horigan, Hans W. Weigert), 1959-1973 (Folder 47)
  - Gerald, Rex E., 1960 (Folder 48)
  - German Information Center, 1961-1962 (Folder 49)
  - Germany. Embassy (United States). See German Information Center
  - Gerth, Hans, 1958 (Folder 50)
  - Giangiacomo Feltrinelli Editore, 1964-1967 (Box 20., Folder 1)
  - Gih, Marcus, 1956-1957 (Folder 2)
  - Gimburtag, Jurgu and Marija, 1960 (Folder 3)
  - Giulio Einaudi Editore, 1957-1963 (Folder 4)
  - Glazer, Nathan, 1957-1961 (Folder 5)
  - Gliksman, Jerzy, 1956 (Folder 6)
  - Gluckstein, Ygael, 1954-1961 (Folder 7)
  - Goblot, Henri, 1963 (Folder 8)
  - Goldberg, Harry, 1958-1959 (Folder 9)
  - Goldberg, Z., 1938 (Folder 10)
  - Goldfrank, David M., 1966-1969 (Folder 11)
  - Goldfrank, Esther S. See Wittfogel, Esther S.
  - Goldfrank, Sandy, 1965 (Folder 12)
  - Goldfrank, Sylvia and Max, 1961-1987 (Folder 13)
  - Goldwin, Robert A., 1963 (Folder 14)
  - Gonzaga University, 1962 (Folder 15)
  - Goodell, Grace E., 1980 (Folder 16)
  - Goodman, Grant K., 1972-1975 (Folder 17)
  - Goodrich, L. Carrington, 1935-1951 (Folder 18)
  - Gordon, Donald F., 1962 (Folder 19)
  - Gordon, Olga K. See Lang, Olga
  - Goske, Manfred, 1972-1986 (Folder 20)
  - Gottfried, Paul, 1973-1974 (Folder 21)
  - Grajdanzev, Andrew J., 1937-1938 (Folder 22)
  - Grammata Editions, 1978-1979. Includes correspondence with Roy N. Schantz (Folder 23)
  - Grant, Alan G., 1955 (Folder 24)
  - Graves, Mortimer, 1937-1940 (Folder 25)
  - Grazia, Alfred de, 1953 (Folder 26)
  - Grazia, Sebastian de, 1953-1973 (Folder 27)
  - Great Britain. Embassy (United States), 1967-1970 (Folder 28)
  - Greene, Roger S., 1940 (Folder 29)
  - Greffrath, Matthias, 1977-1980 (Folder 30)
  - Gregersen, Magnus I., 1955 (Folder 31)
  - Gregg, Alan, 1956 (Folder 32)
  - Gross, Feliks, 1956-1984 (Folder 33)
  - Grubert, Wilhelm, n.d. (Folder 34)
  - Grunebaum, G. E. Von, 1943-1948 (Folder 35)
  - Grunert, Karl, 1946-1949 (Folder 36)
  - Guilde, 1964-1965 (Folder 37)
  - Gulik, R. H. van, 1936 (Folder 38)
  - Gumbel, E. J., 1952 (Folder 39)
  - Gumperz, Julian, 1948-1963 (Folder 40)
  - Gunn, Edward, 1981 (Folder 41)
  - Gunther, Edmund, n.d. (Folder 42)
  - Gunther, Erna, 1949-1967 (Folder 43)
  - Gurney, Natalie, 1948 (Folder 44)
  - HRAF Press, 1957-1958 (Box 21., Folder 1)
  - Hackenberg, Robert A., 1956-1964 (Folder 2)
  - Haetzel, Klaus J., 1971 (Folder 3)
  - Hahne, Margot and Hans-Joachim, 1976 (Folder 4)
  - Halbach, Otto, 1947-1949 (Folder 5)
  - Hallowell, A. Irving, 1946-1947 (Folder 6)
  - Haloun, G., 1949 (Folder 7)
  - Hamline University, 1956 (Folder 8)
  - Handke, Werner, 1958-1959 (Folder 9)
  - Handy, Craighill E. S., 1946-1954 (Folder 10)
  - Harcourt, Brace and Company (Fred D. Wieck), 1951-1962 (Folder 11)
  - Harding College, 1957-1959 (Folder 12)
  - Hardy, E. R., Jr., 1945 (Folder 13)
  - Harlow, Brooks, 1960 (Folder 14)
  - Harper and Row (Fred D. Wieck, Hugh Van Dusen), 1963-1975 (Folder 15)
  - Harris, Marvin, 1966-1967 (Folder 16)
  - Harrison, James P., Jr., 1961-1966 (Folder 17)
  - Harstick, Hans-Peter, 1970-1971 (Folder 18)
  - Harvard University (Donald C. McKay), 1940-1954 (Folder 19)
  - Harvard University Press (Thomas J. Wilson), 1966 (Folder 20)
  - Haury, Emil W., 1959-1965 (Folder 21)
  - Hausler, Heinrich, 1960 (Folder 22)
  - Hayashi, Kentaro, 1960 (Folder 23)
  - Hayek, Friedrich A. von, 1956 (Folder 24)
  - Hayes, Carlton J. H., 1947 (Folder 25)
  - Hazemann, Robert Henri, 1929-1969 (Folder 26)
  - Heichelheim, F. M., 1949-1951 (Folder 27)
  - Heine, Gertrud and Karolus
    - Undated (Folder 28)
    - 1945-1959 (Folder 29)
    - 1960-1986 (Folder 30)
  - Heiseke, Hans (Folder 31)
  - Henderson, Gregory, 1968 (Box 22., Folder 1)
  - Henke, August, 1958-1963 (Folder 2)
  - Henle, James, 1951-1961 (Folder 3)
  - Henning, W. B., 1949-1966 (Folder 4)
  - Henry Luce Foundation, 1969 (Folder 5)
  - Henry Regnery Company, 1964 (Folder 6)
  - Herbert C. Roseman Publisher, 1970-1971 (Folder 7)
  - Hermann Gentner Verlag, 1957 (Folder 8)
  - Hermens, Ferdinand A., 1967 (Folder 9)
  - Herminges, Josefine, 1947 (Folder 10)
  - Herrfahrdt, Heinrich, 1961 (Folder 11)
  - Herskovits, Melville J., 1947 (Folder 12)
  - Hessami, Aram, 1986 (Folder 13)
  - Hickmann, Charlotte, 1946-1947 (Folder 14)
  - Hielscher, Friedrich and Gertrud, 1929-1978 (Folder 15)
  - Hirano, Yoshitaro, 1935-1951 (Folder 16)
  - Hirsch, Helmut, 1979-1980 (Folder 17)
  - Historical Research Foundation, n.d. (Folder 18)
  - Hitchcock, Robert K., 1972 (Folder 19)
  - Hitti, Philip K., 1950 (Folder 20)
  - Ho, Franklin L., 1936-1937 (Folder 21)
  - Ho, Tzu-chuan, 1949-1951 (Folder 22)
  - Hodanu, Traute, 1950 (Folder 23)
  - Hoebel, E. A., 1960 (Folder 24)
  - Holland, William L., 1938-1951 (Folder 25)
  - Holman, G. Paul, Jr., 1973 (Folder 26)
  - Holzman, Abraham, 1973 (Folder 27)
  - Hong Kong University Press, 1959 (Folder 28)
  - Honigmann, John J., 1955 (Folder 29)
  - Hook, Sidney, 1952-1981 (Folder 30)
  - Hoover Institution (Dennis L. Bark, W. Glenn Campbell, Peter Duignan, Stefan T. Possony, C. Easton Rothwell), 1953-1974 (Folder 31)
  - Hoover Institution Library and Archives (John T. Ma, Franz G. Lassner, Arline Paul, Agnes Peterson, Witold S. Sworakowski, Mary C. Wright, Eugene Wu), 1958-1973 (Folder 32)
  - Horkheimer, Max, 1935-1972 (Folder 33)
  - Hornbeck, Stanley K., 1959 (Folder 34)
  - Horowitz, Irving Louis, 1965-1966 (Folder 35)
  - Hou, Chi-ming, 1958 (Folder 36)
  - Howe, Irving, 1968 (Folder 37)
  - Hsiang, Paul S., 1947 (Folder 38)
  - Hsiao, Kung-chuan, 1953-1965 (Folder 39)
  - Hsiao, Tso-liang, 1964 (Folder 40)
  - Hsii, Francis, 1940 (Folder 41)
  - Hsing, Siping, 1935 (Folder 42)
  - Hu, C. T., 1957-1961 (Folder 43)
  - Hu, Chiu-yuan, 1956-1968 (Box 23., Folder 1)
  - Hu, Shih, 1935-1943 (Folder 2)
  - Hu Shih Memorial Scholarship Fund, 1962 (Folder 3)
  - Huang, K. Loo, 1952 (Folder 4)
  - Hucker, Charles O., 1963 (Folder 5)
  - Hudson, G. F., 1957 (Folder 6)
  - Hudson Institute (Herman Kahn), 1962-1964 (Folder 7)
  - Hughes, E. R., 1946-1947 (Folder 8)
  - Human Resources Research Office, 1954 (Folder 9)
  - Hung, William, 1935-1939 (Folder 10)
  - Hunter, Edward, 1954-1960 (Folder 11)
  - Huntington, Ellsworth, 1939-1942 (Folder 12)
  - Hurewitz, Jacob C., 1961 (Folder 13)
  - Huttenbach, Henry R., 1959-1961 (Folder 14)
  - Ichiro, Kudo, 1979 (Folder 15)
  - Ilgner, Renate and Eleonore, 1948-1973. See also Morgenthau, Irma T. (Folder 16)
  - Imported Publications and Products, 1953-1962 (Folder 17)
  - India. Permanent Mission to the United Nations, 1952 (Folder 18)
  - Indian Council for Cultural Relations, 1961 (Folder 19)
  - Indiana University (Cecil C. Brett, S. Y. Teng), 1959-1969 (Folder 20)
  - Indiana University Press, 1951-1952 (Folder 21)
  - Indice, 1960 (Folder 22)
  - Ingram, James C., 1970 (Folder 23)
  - Inkeles, Alex, 1959-1961 (Folder 24)
  - Inouye, Shin-ichi, 1958-1961 (Folder 25)
  - Institut fur Auslandsbeziehungen, 1958-1959 (Folder 26)
  - Institute for Social Science Research, 1967 (Folder 27)
  - Institute of Asian Economic Affairs, 1961 (Folder 28)
  - Institute of Chinese Culture (Cheng Chi-pao), 1969-1971 (Folder 29)
  - Institute of Pacific Relations, 1934-1950. See also Carter, Edward C.; Field, Frederick V.; Holland, William L.; Jaffe, Philip J. (Folder 30)
  - Institute on the Nature of Communism (Ewing P. Shahan), 1962-1967 (Folder 31)
  - Intercollegiate Society of Individualists, 1960 (Folder 32)
  - Intercollegiate Studies Institute, 1966-1986 (Folder 33)
  - International Commission Against Forced Labour Camps, 1956-1961 (Folder 34)
  - International Congress of Orientalists (John King Fairbank, Russell H. Fifield), 1963-1967 (Folder 35)
  - International Institute for Social History (Werner Blumenberg, Frits Kool), 1955-1970. See also Lehning, Arthur (Folder 36)
  - International Political Science Association, 1957-1959 (Folder 37)
  - International Scholarly Book Services, 1973-1975 (Folder 38)
  - International Society for Oriental Research, 1962 (Folder 39)
  - Internationale Literatur, 1938-1939 (Folder 40)
  - Ishikawa, Tadao, 1958 (Folder 41)
  - Isis (I. Bernard Cohen, George Sarton), 1948-1949 (Folder 42)
  - Israel Emergency Fund, 1973 (Folder 43)
  - Istituto Italo Cinese (Alberto Pieri), 1972 (Folder 44)
  - Iwamura, Shinobu, 1958 (Folder 45)
  - J. C. B. Mohr/Paul Siebeck, 1971 (Box 24., Folder 1)
  - Jackson, Barbara Ward, 1965-1967 (Folder 2)
  - Jackson, W. A. Douglas, 1964-1971 (Folder 3)
  - Jacobi, Lotte. See Reiss-Jacobi, Lotte
  - Jacobs, Norman G., 1950-1965 (Folder 4)
  - Jacobsen, Thorkild, 1949 (Folder 5)
  - Jacobson, Harold W., 1966 (Folder 6)
  - Jacoby, Eduard G., 1969-1973 (Folder 7)
  - Jacoby, Peter and Ilse, 1969 (Folder 8)
  - Jaeger, Hans, 1953-1962 (Folder 9)
  - Jaffe, Philip J. and Agnes, 1937-1976 (Folder 10)
  - Jansen, Marius B., 1954-1979 (Folder 11)
  - Japan. Consulate (New York), 1959-1960 (Folder 12)
  - Japan. Embassy (United States), 1954 (Folder 13)
  - Japan Institute of Foreign Affairs, 1958 (Folder 14)
  - Japan Interpreter, 1971 (Folder 15)
  - Jeffery, A., 1948 (Folder 16)
  - Jellinek, Frank, 1949 (Folder 17)
  - Jessup, John K., 1957 (Folder 18)
  - Jessup, Philip C., 1949-1950 (Folder 19)
  - Jettmar, Karl, 1978 (Folder 20)
  - Jewish Theological Seminary of America, 1957 (Folder 21)
  - Joffe, Olga. See Lang, Olga
  - Johanneum Luneburg. See Goske, Manfred and Senne, Wolfgang
  - John C. Lincoln Institute (James R. Brown), 1968-1969 (Folder 22)
  - John Simon Guggenheim Memorial Foundation, 1958-1972 (Folder 23)
  - Johns Hopkins Press, 1953-1954 (Folder 24)
  - Johns Hopkins University, 1953-1981 (Folder 25)
  - Johnson, D. Gale, 1962 (Folder 26)
  - Johnson, Frederick, 1970-1973 (Folder 27)
  - Johnsson, Stephen H., 1962 (Folder 28)
  - Jones, Alfred Winslow, 1958-1963 (Folder 29)
  - Jones, Garth N., 1972 (Folder 30)
  - Jones, Jack, 1959 (Folder 31)
  - Jones, Rogan, 1961 (Folder 32)
  - Jones, Stephen B., 1958 (Folder 33)
  - Jong, Fr. de, 1971 (Folder 34)
  - Jong, Rudolf de, 1970 (Folder 35)
  - Journal of Asian Studies (John A. Harrison, Wilma Fairbank, Earl H. Pritchard, Donald H. Shively), 1947-1969. Includes correspondence with Ardath W. Burks (Folder 36)
  - Journal of Modern History, 1954-1958 (Folder 37)
  - Journal of the American Oriental Society, 1957-1971 (Folder 38)
  - Jouvenel, Bertrand de, 1954-1959 (Folder 39)
  - Judd, Walter H., 1957-1971 (Folder 40)
  - Jungblut, Gerd W., 1979 (Folder 41)
  - Junius Verlag, 1985 (Folder 42)
  - KDK Kojimachi Institute (Etsuo Kohtani), 1965-1969 (Box 25., Folder 1)
  - KIRO-TV, 1959 (Folder 2)
  - Kalous, Milan, 1970-1975 (Folder 3)
  - Kamei, Tomu, 1962-1966 (Folder 4)
  - Kamenka, Eugene, 1969-1972 (Folder 5)
  - Kammler, Hans, 1967-1973 (Folder 6)
  - Kantorowicz, Alfred, 1957-1968 (Folder 7)
  - Kao, Marcel, 1958-1959 (Folder 8)
  - Karlgren, Bernhard, 1949-1950 (Folder 9)
  - Kassner, Ernest, 1961 (Folder 10)
  - Kato, Kanju, 1949-1950 (Folder 11)
  - Katz, Julius J., 1957-1959 (Folder 12)
  - Katz, Solomon, 1960-1966 (Folder 13)
  - Kautsky, Benedikt, 1954-1959 (Folder 14)
  - Kautsky, John H., 1962 (Folder 15)
  - Kawashima, Takeyoshi, 1950 (Folder 16)
  - Keehn, Deborah, 1966-1968 (Folder 17)
  - Keh, Chi-yang, 1947-1948 (Folder 18)
  - Kendall, Walter, 1962 (Folder 19)
  - Kendall, Willmoore, 1963 (Folder 20)
  - Kennan, George F., 1972 (Folder 21)
  - Kennedy, George A., 1939-1947 (Folder 22)
  - Kennedy, William D., 1952-1955 (Folder 23)
  - Kerner, Robert J., 1950 (Folder 24)
  - Kersten, Kurt, 1948 (Folder 25)
  - Kertesz, Stephen D., 1956-1967 (Folder 26)
  - Kidder, A. V., 1946-1950 (Folder 27)
  - Kierman, Frank, 1947-1958 (Folder 28)
  - Kim, Chong Sun, 1965-1966 (Folder 29)
  - Kim, Hyun Kil, 1966-1967 (Folder 30)
  - Kimball, Alan, 1976 (Folder 31)
  - Kindt, Werner, 1971-1976 (Folder 32)
  - Kintner, William R., 1959-1960 (Folder 33)
  - Kirby, E. Stuart, 1959 (Folder 34)
  - Kirchhoff, Paul, 1942-1951 (Folder 35)
  - Kirk, Grayson, 1957 (Folder 36)
  - Kirkpatrick, Evron M., 1951-1966 (Folder 37)
  - Kirkpatrick, Jeane J., 1957-1963 (Folder 38)
  - Kirschner, Alfred, 1947 (Folder 39)
  - Kisselgoff, Lea Mering, 1959-1970 (Folder 40)
  - Kissinger, Henry A., 1959-1967 (Folder 41)
  - Klatt, Dietrich and Edel, 1968-1987 (Folder 42)
  - Klatt, Holger, n.d. (Folder 43)
  - Klatt, Milli
    - Undated (Box 26., Folder 1)
    - 1917-1969 (Folder 2)
    - 1970-1984 (Folder 3)
  - Klatt, Werner, 1967 (Folder 4)
  - Klein, Guillermo Walter, 1961-1963 (Folder 5)
  - Kluckhohn, Clyde, 1948-1950 (Folder 6)
  - Knauth, Lothar E., 1967 (Folder 7)
  - Knopfelmacher, Frank, 1970 (Folder 8)
  - Knorr, Klaus, 1960 (Folder 9)
  - Kohlberg, Alfred, 1954-1959 (Folder 10)
  - Kohn, Hans, 1954 (Folder 11)
  - Konau, Walter, 1975-1977 (Folder 12)
  - Kool, Frits
    - Undated (Folder 13)
    - 1957-1959 (Folder 14)
    - 1960 (Folder 15)
    - 1961 (Folder 16)
    - 1962 (Folder 17)
    - 1963-1965 (Box 27., Folder 1)
    - 1966-1972 (Folder 2)
  - Kornfeder, Joseph T., 1952 (Folder 3)
  - Kornhauser, David H., 1958 (Folder 4)
  - Korsch, Karl, 1947-1950 (Folder 5)
  - Korzec, Michel, 1978 (Folder 6)
  - Kosterlitz, Hanna, 1959 (Folder 7)
  - Kosthorst, Erich, 1983 (Folder 8)
  - Kracke, Edward A., Jr., 1948-1961 (Folder 9)
  - Krader, Lawrence, 1945-1954 (Folder 10)
  - Kraemer, Fritz G. A. and Britta, 1967-1969 (Folder 11)
  - Kramer, Samuel Noah, 1949 (Folder 12)
  - Kramers, J. H., 1951 (Folder 13)
  - Kraus, Wolfgang, 1978-1986 (Folder 14)
  - Kreye, Helene
    - Undated (Folder 15)
    - 1914 (Folder 16)
    - 1915 (Folder 17)
    - 1946-1949 (Folder 18)
    - 1950-1959 (Folder 19)
    - 1960-1974 (Folder 20)
  - Kristof, Ladis K. D., 1960-1983 (Box 28., Folder 1)
  - Kroeber, Alfred L., 1946-1960 (Folder 2)
  - Kruckenberg, Adolf, 1949 (Folder 3)
  - Kruse, Hans, 1947-1975 (Folder 4)
  - Kubek, Anthony, 1961-1973 (Folder 5)
  - Kublin, Hyman, 1950 (Folder 6)
  - Kudo, Ichiro, 1979 (Folder 7)
  - Kuehnelt-Leddihn, Erik Ritter von, 1958 (Folder 8)
  - Kurbjuhn, Kornelia, 1979 (Folder 9)
  - LaDany, L., 1958-1986 (Folder 10)